Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
Larry Gelbart papers
1940-2007
UCLA Library Special Collections
Gelbart, Larry
PASC.0022
191.2 Linear Feet (384 boxes) (Library has boxes 1-151,153-321, 324-338; ser.C: boxes 1-41; ser.T: boxes 1-8)
Collection consists of material related to the career of writer and producer, Larry Gelbart. Includes scripts, treatments, production material, scrapbooks, clippings, correspondence, photographs, and video and audio tapes. Contains material from radio, television, theater, and motion picture productions such as City of angels (stage), The Bob Hope show (radio), A funny thing happened on the way to the forum (stage), M*A*S*H (television), and Tootsie (motion picture).
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942330673606533
Biography/History
Larry Simon Gelbart was born in Chicago, IL, Feb. 25, 1923-28 (sources vary); at age 16 he began comedy writing for radio's Maxwell House Coffee Times; from 1946-52, he continued writing for a variety of radio series such as "Duffy's Tavern" (1946), "Command Performance" (1946-47), and "The Bob Hope Show" (1949-52); started writing for television in 1950 and worked on shows including "The Red Buttons Show" and "Caesar's Television Comedy Hour"; started his career playwr iting in the early 1960s with the theatrical comedy, "The Conquering Hero" (1960); helped develop the television series "M*A*S*H" in 1972 and continued to work on the show until 1976 when he left to pursue other projects; the winner of many awards and honors, Gelbart has authored or co-authored numerous projects including the plays, "A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Forum" (1963), "Mastergate" (1989), "And City Of Angels" (1989), and the screenplays "Oh, God!" (1977) and "Tootsie" (1984).
Scope and Content
Collection consists of material related to the career of writer and producer, Larry Gelbart. Includes scripts, treatments, production material, scrapbooks, clippings, correspondence, photographs, and video and audio tapes. Contains material from radio, television, theater, and motion picture productionssuch as "City Of Angels" (Stage), "The Bob Hope Show" (Radio), "A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Forum" (stage), "M*A*S*H" (television), and "Tootsie" (motion picture).
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Articles
Awards
Correspondence
Interviews
Personal and Biographical
Printed Materials
Projects
Publications
Speeches
Subject Files
Submitted Materials
Tapes
Writings
Television writers -- United States -- Archives.; Television scripts; Television producers and directors -- United States -- Archives.; Screenwriters -- United States -- Archives.; Screenplays; Radio writers -- United States -- Archives.; M*A*S*H (Television program); Dramatists, American -- 20th century -- Archives.; Archives; Gelbart, Larry--Archives
- Articles
  - Dukakis, Michael (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 11)
    Scope and Contents note
    Op/Ed Piece for Los Angeles Times, Supporting Michael Dukakis in 1988 Presidential Primaries, May 20, 1988. 6 drafts, some with annotations. - Handwritten message to Janet Clayton, Op/Ed section.
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box Ser. C-2, Folder 12)
    "Japan Buys a Used President," aka "ERR:Emperor Ronald Reagan," New York Times Op/Ed by Larry Gelbart, 1989. 7 drafts, some w/ annotations. - Short version, for a Beverly Hills Library Reading, 10/28/90, 2 copies. - Correspondence re: article.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 2)
    "Playwrights for President." Article by Larry Gelbart for Mirabella, July 1990, 2 p. - Copy editor's draft, with annotations. Drafts (7): 1 marked "final 3/26/90," 4 p. - Packet of "roughs and notes," no date.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 3)
    By Larry Gelbart for Hollywood Reporter. - "Funny People" by Steve Allen, 2/5/82 (3 drafts, 2 published). - "Screening Sickness" by Ernie Lehman, 10/17/82 (typed original, published copy). - Quote for Susan Sorenson book review.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 4)
    "TV Guidance" by Larry Gelbart for Vogue, February 1985. 2 pages. -Published copies (2 + cover art). - Typed drafts, 3 copies, one with annotations, no dates. - MS notes, annotated in red, no date.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 5)
    Article about Woody Allen for Jean Penn of Playboy. Written by Larry Gelbart. Typed drafts, 3/6/90, 3 copies, one with annotations. MS draft, 3/6/90.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 6)
    Notes for an Esquire article, some typed, some handwritten, 2 packets. No date. Annotations.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 7)
    "How I Spent my Summer Vacation." Article for TV Guide by Larry Gelbart, Sept 22-28, 1956. 3 1/2 published copies, 1 typed original (4 p.)
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 8)
    "Audacious. Satirical. Hip. Sophisticated. Wonderfully Silly." Review of the It's Garry Shandling's Show, by Larry Gelbart, 05/16/87. 1 1/2 published copies, marked w/ letter to Gelbart re: Joan Rivers. - Drafts (3), Correspondence, notes. TV Guide
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 9)
    Outlined notes for possible article, annotated, 4 p. - Blank Freelance contract with US Magazine, no date.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 8)
    "Peering Through the Tube Darkly..." Article by Larry Gelbart re: Rodney King, New York Times, April 16, 1995. - Notes for "What literature most influence you as a child?" 1988.
  - Perot, Ross (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 9)
    "Perot's Ticket to the White House." Article written by Larry Gelbart for New York Times, June 16, 1992.
  - Clinton, William Jefferson (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 10)
    "Summit Upon Summit" by Larry Gelbart and "Let's Get Undepressed" by Spaulding Gray for the New York Times, January 17, 1993. Articles about the election and inauguration of Bill Clinton.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 4)
    Articles that span the first third of Gelbart's career (1944-1968).-Topics include: Duffy's Tavern, Sid Caesar, Judy Garland, Bob Hope, etc.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 5)
    Articles from time spent in England, 1968-1978 (approx.). Topics include, Queen Elizabeth & Prince Philip, M*A*S*H, A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, & Oh God!
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 6)
    Articles from 1982 to 1991. Topics include: End of M*A*S*H, AfterM*A*S*H, United States, City of Angels, etc.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 8)
    Rolling Stone: Letter to the Editor, May 13, 1985, 3 p.
  - Clinton, William Jefferson (Box Ser. C-18, Folder 3)
    Campaign report and strategy for Democractic party. Written by Greenberg-Lake, April 15, 1992.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-19, Folder 4)
    Misc news clippings regarding Larry Gelbart and his projects, 1992.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 10)
    Miscellaneous writings by Larry Gelbart for possible tributes and articles. No dates.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 16)
    Nine revisions of an article written for New York Times regarding Art and Life, Spring 1995.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 18)
    June 1995: "The Story Structure Gurus," "A Conversation with Ernest Lehman," "Larry Gelbart Current Events." - March 1996: "Caesar's Hour Revisited."
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 2)
    Review of "Thank You for Smoking," by Larry Gelbart. Appeared in the New York Times Book Review, 1994. Multiple xerox copies of article. - Letters of congratulations re: article.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 9)
    Articles re: Gelbarts. "Author exhibits wit and wisdom at museum," re: reunion at Palm Springs museum. - "Harry at Your Head," re: Harry Gelbart. "Search for a Postmodern Theater," Interviews with playwrights.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 10)
    "An Open Letter to Mr. Larry Gelbart," a response by J. David Miles. - Numerous drafts of a rebuttal to the letter by Larry Gelbart. Articles appeared in The Journal, December/January 1992.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-26, Folder 1)
    Articles written for Harpers. Two on City of Los Angeles, one on Palm Springs and one on Birthdays, 1993.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-26, Folder 2)
    Contract between Gelbart and Harpers Bazaar, correspondence and a few drafts of articles, including "Palm Spring." 1993.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-26, Folder 3)
    "Ten Out of Fifty," article by Larry Gelbart for Emmy magazine, regarding the first fifty years of television, January 8, 1996. Includes letter from Emmy.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-26, Folder 4)
    Vanity Fair, Special Hollywood Issue, April 1995.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 2)
    Handwritten notes, marked "Random thoughts, I guess in response to questions long forgotten." No date, 7 pages.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 8)
    Miscellaneous articles about Larry Gelbart. 1996.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 20)
    Articles about Larry Gelbart: Gelbart and the Writers Guild of America, Jolie Memoire (race horse owned by Gelbart), Being a judge for the Ten Best Films (Premiere, March 1992), "Network" and CBS, etc.
  - Lehman, Ernest (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 34)
    Notes for a possible foreward. Handwritten draft. No date. Annotated in red ink.
  - Articles about Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 16)
    Copy of an article in the Journal of the Writers Guild of America, Dec. 1997-Jan. 1998.
  - Articles by Larry Gelbart (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 19)
    Untitled, undated essay re: artists/writers in politics at the occasion of Vaclav Havel's speech before a joint session of of the House and the Senate.
  - Gregory Dunne/The Monster (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 24)
    Book review for the New York Times, March 2, 1997 for John Gregory Dunne's book. Incl. advance uncorrected proof copy.
- Awards
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-3, Folder 16)
    Program: Union College Commencement Excercises, June 15, 1986, Schectady, New York. Larry Gelbart received an honorary Doctor of Arts degree.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 1)
    Vetty Awards, Presented at the U.S.S. Intrepid Sea-Air-Space Museum, October 31, 1990. Presented by The Vietnam Veterens Ensemble Theatre Company. Vetty Award Presented to Larry Gelbart and accepted by Loretta Swit.
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Award Dinner (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 2)
    "Pay the Two Million Dollars." Written by Larry Gelbart, performed by Walther and Charles Matthau, for the ADA Foundation's First Annual Eleanor Award Dinner, April 3, 1982. - Includes scripts, 10 p.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 3)
    Pacific Pionner Broadcasters, Silver Anniversary, January 1991 (Gelbart was honored in 1987). - Larry Gelbart Film Retrospective, USC, 1990. - 1983 British Academy of Film and Television Arts Awards Ceremony, 3/19 & 3/25/84 (Gelbart was nominated).
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-4, Folder 20)
    Palm Street Walk of Stars. Correspondence regarding the placement and engraving of the star in Palm Springs, June 6, 1995.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-6, Folder 11)
    Transcript of speech given at the Tony Awards, 1990. 3 copies, 4 pages each.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-8, Folder 10)
    "Junior Ad Club, Spotlight on Achievement, Script #9." Award given to Larry Gelbart by the Junior Advertising Club of Los Angeles (1950). Transcript of Radio presentation. Includes skit of how Gelbart got his start in writing. 8 pages.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-11, Folder 5)
    Beverly Hills Theatre Guild Roast. Correspondence, 2 Programs, Guest List, & Speech (Notes and typed copy, 2 p.), Proclimations by County of Los Angeles, Governor of California, US Congress, City of Beverly Hills, City of Los Angeles, et al.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-11, Folder 6)
    AfterM*A*S*H Awards: Humanitas nomination. - People for the American Way (1987). - Laurel Award. - People's Choice Award (1984). - Academy of Television Arts and Sciences. - Beverly Hills Theatre Guild.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-11, Folder 13)
    Correspondence regarding 30th Annual Christopher Awards. Larry Gelbart was awarded for Movie Movie, 1979.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-15, Folder 6)
    Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters lunch, May 15, 1987. Notes for a speech given by Larry Gelbart.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-18, Folder 4)
    Awards: Pritikin Masters Certificate, October 3, 1991, "in recognition of continued commitment to opitmal health. - Producers Guild of America, award for M*A*S*H, March 2, 1992.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-24, Folder 22)
    Award nominations for City of Angeles: Tony Award and Edgar Allen Poe Award. 1994.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 5)
    National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences. Nomination for Outstanding Writing Achievement in Comedy for the M*A*S*H Pilot. For the 1972-3 Emmys.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-25, Folder 6)
    Writers Guild of America Annual Award, Nomination for Television Writing Achievement for Adapted Long Form for "Barbarians at the Gate," 1993. - Certificate and invitation.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-32, Folder 6)
    Final guest list for the Writers Guild Tribute to Larry Gelbart, January 28, 1997.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-32, Folder 7)
    Correspondence regarding finalization of guest and host list. November 1996 - January 1997
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-32, Folder 8)
    Correspondence regarding script for the Writers Guild Tribute to Larry Gelbart. November 1996 - January 1997.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-32, Folder 9)
    Writers Guild of America Tribute to Larry Gelbart, revised final script, January 24, 1997. - Script, as of January 14, 1997. Produced by Michael Hirsch.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-32, Folder 10)
    Publicty and articles relating to the Writers Guild of America Tribute to Larry Gelbart, January 1997.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-33, Folder 1)
    Resolution Honoring Larry Gelbart, signed by Gray Davis, Lt. Governor of California, January 28, 1997. Part of the Writers Guild of America Tribute to Larry Gelbart.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-34, Folder 24)
    Photograph of Larry Gelbart, Walter Halsey Davis, Vikie Patik and two unidentified people holding their award plaques from the Writers Guild of America. Gelbart won for "Barbarians at the Gate."
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-35, Folder 21)
    Program and invitation to the Writers Guild of America Tribute to the Writer - Lifetime of Career Excellence, January 28, 1997.
  - Awards (Box Ser. C-37, Folder 1)
    Congratulatory notes and other related items, March 1998, re Tribute to Larry Gelbart.
  - Duke Ellington Awards, 1999 Feb (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - MASTERGATE - Golden Gate Award (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Honorable Mention for Television Comedy category. Awarded at the 36th San Francisco International Film Festival, 04/29 - 05/13/93.
  - ACADEMY AWARDS
    - 57th Annual (Box 155, Folder 9)
      Correspondence regarding the Phil Collins controversy, 1985. - Two Rolling Stone articles. - List of "Song-Singers, 1934-1983." 3 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 155, Folder 10)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten first draft, February 28, 1985, 138 pages.
    - 58th Annual (Box 155, Folder 13)
      Scripts (4) presenting screenwriting awards. - Scripts (3), handwritten draft and typed drafts, for presenters Alan Alda and Jane Fonda. Correspondence with AMPAS.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 1)
      Script: First draft and schedule "as of 3/8/85" and with copious annotations. - Timings and voice over narrations. - Material for the Technical Awards.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 2)
      Script revisions, dated February to March 1985. 15 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 3)
      Show rundowns, 02/19/85 - 03/21/85. 11 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 4)
      Timetables, dated August 1984 - January 1985. 4 items.
    - 56th Annual (Box 161, Folder 5)
      Ratings research for 1984 Academy Awards (04/24/84). - Short rundown, "As broadcast," 1984. 2 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 6)
      Pamphlet - regarding National Endowment for the Arts Award, 1985. - Memoranda - List of music rights archived by NEA (02/19/85). - Typed version of pamphlet. 3 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 7)
      Lists of potential presenters for the 1985 show.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 8)
      Letter to Robert Selig re trailer completion (2/14/85), 2 p. - "Fact Sheet," n.d., 5 p. - "Academy Announces Nominations for 57th Oscar Awards," n.d., 13 p. 3 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 161, Folder 9)
      Correspondence and publicity, 10 items, re the honorary award to David L. Wolper (03/13/85), 7 p. - Correspondence regarding the exclusion of MPAA President (02/15/85) (3 letters).
    - 58th Annual (Box 162, Folder 1)
      Final Script with crew and cast contact lists, dated 03/17/86. Marked "Revised 3/21 -- Revised 3/22." 257 pages.
    - 57th Annual (Box 162, Folder 2)
      Nominations for Awards Ceremony for the Documentary and Foreign categories, February 1985. Includes xeroxed reviews of the nominated films. 22 pages.
    - 57th Annual (Box 162, Folder 3)
      Board of Governors' Ball program. - Tickets to the Ball. Program for Awards Ceremony. - Backstage passes (3) for Larry Gelbart.
    - 57th Annual (Box 166, Folder 8)
      Script As Broadcast, Domestic. March 25 1985. 233+ pages.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 3)
      Continuity for the telecast. No date. 4 pages. - "Additional Names for Friends of Oscar -- or Special Presentors," 1 page.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Articles regarding the low ratings for broadcast. March through April 1985. 20 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, 20 items, 02/15/85 - 04/16/85. Regarding Nominees Luncheon, Rehearsals, the Telecast, Possible presenters.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Both first drafts, annotated, February 28 1985, 103 p. 2 items.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. As Broadcast, International, 03/25/85, 106 p.
    - 57th Annual (Box 173, Folder 8)
      Production book: Master copy of script, staff list, schedules, show rundown, and final script, dated 03/25/85.
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1999 July - Aug (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1998 Dec - 1999 Mar (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1998 Dec - 1999 Mar (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1999 June (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 Aug (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Jan - May (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Jan - May (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Dec - 1999 Mar (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 July - Aug (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Apr - July (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Apr - July (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Apr - June (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Apr - June (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Jay Malarcher, 1997-1998 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Lord James Hanson, 1996-1998 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 June (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 July - Sept (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Aug - Oct (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Sept - Oct (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Donna Mae Balkan (Litowitz), 1944-1945 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 Dec - 2000 Feb (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2000 Jan - April (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Nov - Dec (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Nov - Dec (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 June - Sept (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1999 Sept - Oct (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Hanson - correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Nov - Dec (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Jan (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Jan (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Creative Artists Agency Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Creative Artists Agency Correspondence, 2000 June - Sept (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2000 July - Aug (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2000 July - Sept (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2000 Jan - March (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000 July - Sept (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), 2000-2001 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), 2000-2001 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), 2000-2001 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 3), 2000 Nov -2001 Apr (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 3), 2000 Nov -2001 Apr (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 3 of 3), 2000 Nov -2001 Apr (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2000 Nov - Dec (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000 Oct - 2001 Mar (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001 Apr - June (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2001 Mar (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 2000 Oct - Dec (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 2000 Oct - Dec (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002 July (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 June (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002 July (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Apr - May (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 June - Aug (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Mar - Apr (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Apr - June (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Apr - June (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Aug (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2002 May - July (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Sept - Oct (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Sept - Oct (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 July - Sept (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Oct - Nov (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Aug - Sept (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2001 May - June (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2001 June (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Mar - Apr (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001 Sept - 2002 Mar (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 Jan (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2001 Sept - Oct (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001 July - Aug (Box 244, Folder 1)